

PROFILE

With more than 9 years of IT experience including a degree major of Web Design/Development. I am a well-rounded technical personality that currently works as an Enterprise Web Developer, also in backend development (Server management, MySQL, PHP) along with knowledge of database language that connects the front-end application to the back-end to collect data from the end user.

CONTACT

PHONE: 501-247-6443

WEBSITE:

www.michaeldgray.com

EMAIL:

mgray2@ualr.edu

SKILLS

Html / CSS / JavaScript Linux / Windows Troubleshooting / Analytical ESXI / vSphere PHP / WordPress / CMS

MICHAEL GRAY

Systems Administrator

EDUCATION

University of Arkansas at Little Rock

8/2020 – present Bachelor of Arts Web Design/Development

Pulaski Technical College

8/2013 – 12/2015 Associates Degree Comp Info Systems: Networking

WORK EXPERIENCE

Univ of Arkansas at Little Rock | Enterprise Web Developer

04/2022 - Present

Manage campus CMS and backend development to provide seamless access and success for students and employees on the UALR website.

Univ of Arkansas at Little Rock | Systems Administrator

06/2019 – 4/2022

Manage campus systems and endpoints to provide continued access and success for students and employees.

Windstream Communications | Network Analyst

4/2019 - 6/2019

Provided network device configuration and maintenance for Fiber to the Tower issues in reported areas to provide internet services.

SCA Pharmaceutical | Network Administrator

06/2019 - 2/2020

Support the corporate network infrastructure and troubleshoot network connectivity issues that arise at multiple LR sites that utilize network devices.

Arkansas Foundation for Medical Care | IT Support Specialist

06/2016 - 2/2019

Support the corporate network infrastructure and troubleshoot network connectivity issues that arise at multiple LR sites that utilize network devices.

Dep of Human Services | Unified Communications Specialist

06/2015 - 06/2016

Support DHS Skype for Business phone system on the main campus and Behavioral Health Hospital. Create and run seminars to help users better.

Windstream Communications | Network Analyst II

12/2012 - 04/2015

Provided network device configuration for DSLAM rollouts in new areas to provide internet services.